<?xml version="1.0"?>
<document xmlns="http://maven.apache.org/XDOC/2.0" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://maven.apache.org/XDOC/2.0 http://maven.apache.org/xsd/xdoc-2.0.xsd">
	<properties>
		<title>About</title>
		<author>André Rouél</author>
	</properties>
	<body>

		<section name="What is UADetector?">
			<p>
				UADetector is a library to detect over 190 different desktop and mobile browsers and 130 other User-Agents like
				feed readers and email clients.
			</p>
			<p>
				The UADetector library is a free, portable Java library to analyze User-Agent strings. The goal of this library is
				to detect the type and the associated operating system of a client like "Mobile Safari 5.1" on "iOS".
			</p>
			<p>
				UADetector not only detects user-agents such as browser, but also robots as Google Bot or Yahoo Bot.
			</p>
			<p>
				The UADetector library is divided into two modules. The
				<a href="modules/uadetector-core/index.html">core module</a>
				includes the API and implementation to read the detection information and the functions to identify User-Agents. The
				<a href="modules/uadetector-resources/index.html">resources module</a>
				contains the database with the necessary identification information and a service factory class to get simply
				preconfigured UserAgentStringParser singletons. This library will be published monthly, is integration-tested
				against the core module and is guaranteed to run against the defined core.
			</p>
		</section>
		<section name="Features">
			<div class="feature">
				<img src="./images/feature.png" alt="Devices" />
				<span class="title">Detects over 190 different browsers</span>
				<p>This library detects over 190 different desktop and mobile browsers and 130 other User-Agents like feed readers,
					multimedia players and email clients.
				</p>
			</div>
			<div class="feature">
				<img src="./images/feature.png" alt="The Robots" />
				<span class="title">Identifies over 900 robots</span>
				<p>On the Internet many robots are on their way to examine sites. A large number of robots can be detected with this
					library.
				</p>
			</div>
			<div class="feature">
				<img src="./images/feature.png" alt="Monthly updated" />
				<span class="title">Monthly updated</span>
				<p>Each month a new version of the resources module will be published so you can always detect the latest
					User-Agents.
				</p>
			</div>
			<div class="feature">
				<img src="./images/feature.png" alt="Extremely tested" />
				<span class="title">Extremely tested</span>
				<p>
					All classes in this library have been especially tested. The unit tests have a 100%
					<a href="modules/uadetector-core/cobertura/index.html">branch coverage</a>
					and 98%
					<a href="modules/uadetector-core/cobertura/index.html">line coverage</a>
					. In addition, many integration tests performed regularly.
				</p>
			</div>
			<br class="clear" />
		</section>
		<section name="How can I help?">
			<p>
				UADetector is an open source tool and welcomes contributions.
			</p>
			<ul>
				<li>
					Report bugs, feature requests and other issues in the
					<a href="./issue-tracking.html">issue tracking</a>
					application.
				</li>
				<li>Help with the documentation by pointing out areas that are lacking or unclear, and if you are so inclined,
					submitting patches to correct it. You can quickly contribute rough thoughts by forking this project on GitHub and
					SourceForge, or you can volunteer to help collate and organize information that is already there.
				</li>
			</ul>
			<p>Your participation in the community is much appreciated!</p>
		</section>

	</body>
</document>
